Guide to the Records of the Office of the Chancellor/Executive Vice President (Borowitz) RG.6.0.7
New York University Archives
- Series III: Development
  - NYU Press, Director, Sep 1975-Aug 1976 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - NYU Press, Director, Sep 1973-Aug 1975 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - NYU Press, Misc, Sep 1974-Sep 1976 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - NYU Press, Misc, Jul 1972-Aug 1974 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - NYU Press, Monthly Reports (Including Operating Statements), Apr 1976-Feb 1977 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - NYU Press, Monthly Reports (Including Operating Statements), Jan 1975-Mar 1976 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - NYU Press, Monthly Reports (Including Operating Statements), Aug 1970-Dec 1974 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - NYU Press, Policy Committee, Oct 1972-Feb 1973 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - NYU Press, Search for Director, Feb 1973-Jul 1973 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - External Affairs, Senior Vice President for, Aug 1971-Apr 1977 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Series IV: Facilities and Services
  The contents of this modest series (.83 linear feet) provide some perspective on the University's plant and associated services and cost concerns. Selected information about academic building maintenance and renovation, Bobst Library, bookstores, computer services, energy needs, housing, planning a student recreation facility, and security appears. Of particular interest is a miscellany of materials concerned with the physical property at the University Heights campus and its disposition, Box 27, folder 12.
  - Administration and Space, Misc, Oct 1973-May 1976 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224963 4
  - Administration and Space, Misc, Jun 1967-Aug 1973 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Services, Correspondence, Reports, Jan 1974-Apr 1976 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Book Center, Jun 1975-Jul 1976 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Book Stores, Feb 1967-Dec 1972 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Computer Services, Sep 1975-May 1976 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Computer Services, Jan 1975-Aug 1975 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Computer Services, Aug 1972-Dec 1974 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Institutional Facilities, Academic Facilities: Bobst Library, Feb 1972-Dec 1975 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Institutional Facilities, Academic Facilities: Bobst Library, Sep 1967-May 1971 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Institutional Facilities, Academic Facilities: Misc (A-F), Sep 1966-Oct 1976 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Institutional Facilities, Academic Facilities: Misc (G-M), Sep 1966-Oct 1976 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Institutional Facilities, Academic Facilities: Misc (O-Z), Sep 1966-Oct 1976 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Institutional Facilities, Academic Facilities: Tisch Hall, Mar 1970-Oct 1975 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224964 2
  - Institutional Facilities, Budget and Financial Matters, Oct 1972-Aug 1976 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Institutional Facilities, Complaints, Apr 1973-Oct 1976 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Institutional Facilities, Energy Crisis, Nov 1974-Jan 1977 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Institutional Facilities, Energy Crisis, Oct 1973-Jul 1974 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Institutional Facilities, Housing, May 1969-May 1976 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Institutional Facilities, Maintenance and Rehabilitation, Nov 1968-Jul 1975 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Institutional Facilities, Misc, Jul 1969-Feb 1977 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Institutional Facilities, Recreational Facilities, May 1972-Sep 1975 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Institutional Facilities, Security, Jan 1974-Jul 1975 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Institutional Facilities, Security, Sep 1967-Sep 1973 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Series V: Finances
  The finances series (2.5 linear feet) includes several matters of note. Box 28, folder 9 contains a paper, "Reflections on Budget Policy, " addressing the loss of the University Heights campus, by Professor Ernest Bloch of GBA, 6/73? Documents in Box 29, folders 1-4, affirm the presence of Vice President for Finance Allan Claxton, appointed 12/75 by President Sawhill and signaling an important shift in responsibility for fiscal matters from the Chancellor.
  Additionally, two subseries were created: Subseries I: Taskforce on the Financial Emergency, Box 29, folders 11-12, and Box 30, folders 1-4; Subseries II: University Heights Campus Disposition, Box 31, folders 1-12, Box 32, folders 1-14, Box 33, folders 1-5. Materials in Box 29, folders 11-12, describe the scope of the University's financial problems in 1975.
  Materials in Box 30, folders 1-5, reflect in part an attempt by NYU to set up a program of engineering education in collaboration with PIB. Box 32, folders 3-4, contains correspondence with NYSED concerning NYU-PIB merger efforts, including, in folder 4, a rejected Hester hand-edited draft agreement, covering so-called negotiable and non-negotiable merger conditions. A summary of agreements reached, including minutes, appears in Box 32, folder 12.
  Further highlighted contents follow Subseries I, namely a collection of materials addressing University finances 1966-1972, created for the Chancellor by Samuel T. Burneson of the President's Office, Box 30, folders 5-11.
  - Sale of University Heights, May 1972-Sep 1973 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Audits and Financial Reports, Aug 1972-Aug 1975 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224965 9
  - Budget Material(All-University), Meetings with Administrators: Summer 1975 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Budget Material (All-University), Meetings with Deans: Summer 1975 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Budget Meetings w/ Deans, VPs, Misc, Jun 1972-Mar 1977 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Budget Reports, Controller's Division, Apr 1974-Nov 1974 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Budget Task Force, Sep 1975-Nov 1975 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Budgets (All-University), Sep 1975-Apr 1977 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Budgets (All-University), Jan 1975-Jun 1975 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Budgets# Misc, Mar 1968-Apr 1976 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Cost Accounting Studies, 1969-1970 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Cost Allocation Procedure, Reports, Jun 1975-Dec 1976 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Finance, Office of the Vice President for, Nov 1976-Mar 1977 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224966 7
  - Finance, Office of the Vice President for, Jul 1976-Oct 1976 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Finance, Office of the Vice President for, Mar 1976-Jun 1976 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Finance, Office of the Vice President for, Jan 1976-Feb 1976 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Finance, Office of the Vice President for, Jun 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Financial Emergency, Misc, Apr 1971-Apr 1973 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Insurance, Nov 1969-Apr 1975 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Investments, Jun 1971-May 1975 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Problems in Higher Education, Nov 1971-Oct 1975 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Subseries I: Task Force on the Financial Emergency
    - Treasurer, Office of the, Jun 1971-Oct 1975 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Task Force on Financial Emergency, Fiscal Review Group 1975, Nov 1975 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Task Force on Financial Emergency, Fiscal Review Group 1975, Oct 1975 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Task Force on Financial Emergency, Fiscal Review Group 1975, Sep 1975 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      barcode: 3 1142 04224967 5
    - Task Force on the Financial Emergency, Fiscal Review Group 1975, Mar 1975-Aug 1975 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Task Force on the Financial Emergency, Jun 1972-Nov 1973 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Task Force on the Financial Emergency, Mar 1972-May 1972 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Materials on University Finances 1966 - 1972 (Files created for Chancellor Borowitz by Samuel T. Burneson) (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Materials on University Finances 1966 - 1972 (Files created for Chancellor Borowitz by Samuel T. Burneson), 1971 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Materials on University Finances 1966 - 1972 (Files created for Chancellor Borowitz by Samuel T. Burneson), 1970 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Materials on University Finances 1966 - 1972 (Files created for Chancellor Borowitz by Samuel T. Burneson), 1969 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Materials on University Finances 1966 - 1972 (Files created for Chancellor Borowitz by Samuel T. Burneson), 1968 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Materials on University Finances 1966 - 1972 (Files created for Chancellor Borowitz by Samuel T. Burneson), 1967 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Subseries II: University Heights Campus Disposition
    - Materials on University Finances 1966 - 1972 (Files created for Chancellor Borowitz by Samuel T. Burneson) (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Center for Interdisciplinary Programs, Jan 1974-Jun 1974 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      barcode: 3 1142 04224968 3
    - Center for Interdisciplinary Programs, Sep 1973-Dec 1973 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Center for Interdisciplinary Programs, May 1973-Aug 1973 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Center for Interdisciplinary Programs, Nov 1972-Apr 1973 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Center for Interdisciplinary Programs, Board of Trustees Minutes, Jun 1973-Dec 1974 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Engineering, NYU School of, Sep 1972-May 1973 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Engineering, NYU School of, Nov 1970-Aug 1972 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Engineering, NYU School of, at Washington Square, Oct 1972-Apr 1973 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Engineering, NYU School of, at Washington Square, May 1972-Sep 1972 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Engineering, NYU School of, Dean, Apr 1972-Oct 1973, Jul 1976 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Engineering, NYU School of, Faculty Meeting Minutes, May 1972May 1973 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Engineering, NYU School of, Merger w/Brooklyn Polytechnic Institute (PIB), Jan 1973-May 1973 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Engineering, NYU School of, Merger w/Brooklyn Polytechnic Institute (PIB), Mar 1972-Nov 1972 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      barcode: 3 1142 04224969 1
    - Merger Agreement, Related Agreements, Jun 1972-Jun 1973 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Merger Agreement, Correspondence, Data, etc., Dec 1972-Sep 1973 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Merger Agreement, Correspondence with New York State Education Department, etc., May 1972-Nov 1972 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Merger Agreement, Drafts, May 1972-Nov 1972 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Merger Agreement, Drafts, Jul 1972 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Merger Agreement, Drafts, Jun 1972 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Merger Agreement, Misc, Jul 1971-Aug 1973 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Merger Agreement, Negotiations: Borowitz Handwritten Notes, undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Merger Agreement, Negotiations: Copy of the Act - Chap. 463, May 1972 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Merger Agreement, Negotiations: NYU Ad Hoc Faculty Committee, May 1972-Feb 1973 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Merger Agreement, Negotiations: Summary of Action and Agreements Reached, Including Minutes, May 1972-Jan 1973 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Merger Agreement, Related Agreements, Oct 1973-Dec 1973 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Negotiations - PIB Annual & Auditors' Reports, 1968, 1971, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - NYU Faculty - Letters of Non- Renewal of Contracts and Reappointment, Aug 1972-Jan 1973 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      barcode: 3 1142 04224970 9
    - NYU Space/Equipment Required, Apr 1972-Jun 1972 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - NYU Student Information, 1972-Jan 1973 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Research and Grants (NYU), May 1973-Aug 1973 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Series VI: Governance
  This series derives its content from the machinery through which the University conducted its business. Within its 3.33 linear feet are materials from primary operating systems (Board of Trustees, President's and Officers' Groups, University Senate), and documents descriptive of initiatives driving their evolution. Faculty union organizing efforts and the transfer of institutional direction from Dr. Hester to Dr. Sawhill had important internal effects, while federal rulemaking governing universities receiving federal funds, for example in the arena of affirmative action, was an important external stimulus for internal change. Materials for/from the above-identified groups as well as a variety of Councils and Commissions, some structural, some topical, are included. The presence of certain materials may signify particular interests of the Chancellor. Agendas may be helpful in identifying and tracking selected topics.
  Formulating institutional agreement on the functions of the (University) Senate was an important governance matter. Box 38, folder 1, contains Report Number Two of a special senate committee on senate powers, 4/10/74, and a response by Dr. Borowitz, 4/30/74. In its report the committee addressed to the Senate its analysis of the question of "proper division of authority among the Board of Trustees, President and Chancellor, Senate, and individual schools," presenting for its consideration a set of "Alternative Models for Development of the Powers of the Senate." Dr. Borowitz, in turn, spells out "philosophical as well as practical difficulties" in administering the University under the proposed model.
  Consideration of some of these concerns, including Senate powers, was ongoing. The 3/15/76 agenda for the President's Weekly Meeting carries a listing of a report on governance by Dr. Borowitz, Box 37, folder 5. "A Report on Governance," by Dr. Borowitz appears again, on the 8/25/76 agenda of the President's Joint Meeting of Deans and Vice Presidents, Box 37, folder 4, where a text is also located.
  University financial matters occupied the Budget Advisory Group between October 1972 and July 1975. A chronological set of agendas, many annotated or "doodled" on by Dr. Borowitz, many with attachments, permits a survey of issues the group considered, Box 33, folder 14, and Box 34, folder 1. An alphabetical, handwritten list suggests that in addition to officers, there were 70 participants, mainly faculty, along with a few students, Box 34, folder 1. A note in Dr. Borowitz' hand on an undated memorandum (summer '75) marks its termination, Box 33, folder 14.
  Continuing attention to university financial matters by the University Senate can be observed in the deliberations and transactions of its Budget Policies Committee, Box 38, folders 11-12, and Box 39, folders 1-5. This committee functioned throughout Dr. Borowitz' term. A name change, from Budget Policies Committee to Financial Affairs Committee, took place effective 9/76. Agendas, again many annotated or "doodled" on by Dr. Borowitz, memoranda, and reports appear; chronological sets of minutes have been transferred to RG 14. The committee's level of involvement can be evaluated by assessing the directness of Chancellor Cartter's memorandum to it of 2/22/72, addressing the dimensions of the University's financial difficulties, and Committee Vice-chair Dr. Ernest Bloch's memorandum of 12/1/72, reporting on deans' responses to a Borowitz query about school budget-making practices, Box 39, folder 5.
  A spectrum of educational matters and the machinery employed and/or created to address them can be tracked through the transactions of the Senate's Educational Policies Committee, Box 39, folders 6-9, Councils and Commissions, All-University Commission on Student Evaluation of Undergraduate Courses, Box 34, folders 8-10, Councils and Commissions, Commission on Undergraduate Education, Box 35, folders 2-8, and Councils and Commissions, Graduate Commission, Box 36, folders 1-9.
  The emergence of a representational body of middle management staff, with roots in the student unrest era of the late 1960's, is somewhat detailed in Box 34, folders 4-7.
  - Research and Grants (PIB), Jun 1972 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees, Sep 1973-Apr 1977 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees, Apr 1971-May 1973 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees, Academic Affairs Committee, Mar 1976-Feb 1977 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees, Academic Affairs Committee, Oct 1975-Feb 1976 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees, By-Laws, Nov 1971-Jun 1973 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees, Financial Affairs Committee, Feb 1973-Dec 1975 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Board of Trustees, Meeting Materials, Mar 1971-Dec 1976 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Board of Trustees, Presidential Search Committee, Nov 1974-Apr 1975 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Budget Advisory Group, Sep 1974-Jul 1975 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Budget Advisory Group, Oct 1972-Jul 1974 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224971 7
  - Committees, University Committee on Inventions and Patents, Dec 1973-Dec 1976 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Councils and Commissions, Administrative Council, Nov 1967-Jun 1969 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Councils and Commissions, Administrative Management Council, Sep 1974-Feb 1976 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Councils and Commissions, Administrative Management Council, Aug 1973-Jul 1974 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Councils and Commissions, Administrative Management Council, Oct 1972-Jun 1973 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Councils and Commissions, Administrative Management Council, Jul 1970-Jun 1972 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Councils and Commissions, All-University Commission on Student Evaluation of Undergraduate Courses, Oct 1974-Oct 1975 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Councils and Commissions, All- University Commission on Student Evaluation of Undergraduate Courses, Apr 1973-Apr 1974 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Councils and Commissions, All-University Commission on Student Evaluation of Undergraduate Courses, Dec 1972-Mar 1973 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Councils and Commissions, Commission on Academic Planning, Oct 1976-Feb 1977 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Councils and Commissions, Commission on Academic Planning, Feb 1976-May 1976 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Councils and Commissions, Commission on Coordinated Liberal Studies, Aug 1973-Feb 1976 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Councils and Commissions, Commission on Coordinated Liberal Studies, Feb 1969-Jun 1973 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224972 5
  - Councils and Commissions, Commission on Undergraduate Education, Mar 1976 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Councils and Commissions, Commission on Undergraduate Education, Jan 1976-Feb 1976 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Councils and Commissions, Commission on Undergraduate Education, Oct 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Councils and Commissions, Commission on Undergraduate Education, Nov 1973-May 1975 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Councils and Commissions, Commission on Undergraduate Education, Sep 1970-Apr 1972 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Councils and Commissions, Commission on Undergraduate Education, Sep 1969-Apr 1970 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Councils and Commissions, Commission on Undergraduate Planning, May 1971-Mar 1976 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Councils and Commissions, Deans' Council, Apr 1974-Jan 1976 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Councils and Commissions, Deans' Council, Jan 1972-Dec 1973 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Councils and Commissions, Deans' Council, Nov 1968-Dec 1971 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Councils and Commissions, Faculty Council, Jul 1976-Feb 1977 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Councils and Commissions, Faculty Council, Oct 1975-May 1976 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Councils and Commissions, Faculty Council, Dec 1973-Aug1975 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Councils and Commissions, Faculty Council, Jun 1972-Apr 1973 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Councils and Commissions, Faculty Council, Feb 1971-May 1972 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Councils and Commissions, Graduate Commission, Sep 1976-Feb 1977 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224973 3
  - Councils and Commissions, May 1976-Aug 1976 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Councils and Commissions, Graduate Commission, Mar 1976-Apr 1976 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Councils and Commissions, Graduate Commission, Oct 1975-Nov 1975 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Councils and Commissions, Graduate Commission, Mar 1975-May 1975 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Councils and Commissions, Graduate Commission, Oct 1974-Nov 1974 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Councils and Commissions, Graduate Commission, Jun 1974 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Councils and Commissions, Graduate Commission, May 1974 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Councils and Commissions, Graduate Commission, Jan 1971-Apr 1973 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Councils and Commissions, Small Deans Council, Sep 1971-Sep 1972 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Councils and Commissions, Washington Square Council, Jan 1971-Nov 1974 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - President/Chancellor, Tuesday Meetings Agendas, Apr 1974-Apr 1975 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - President's Officers Group Meetings, Jul 1973-May 1975 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - President's Officers Group Meetings, Sep 1971-Jun 1973 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - President's Staff Meetings, Action Memoranda, Jun 1975-Feb 1976 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224974 1
  - President's Tuesday Morning Meetings, Jan 1977-Apr 1977 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - President's Weekly Meetings & President's Joint Meetings of Deans and Vice Presidents: Agendas and Minutes, Oct 1976-Jan 1977 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - President's Weekly Meetings & President's Joint Meetings of Deans and Vice Presidents: Agendas and Minutes, Jul 1976-Sep 1976 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - President's Weekly Meetings & President's Joint Meetings of Deans and Vice Presidents: Agendas and Minutes, Feb 1976-Jun 1976 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - University Governance, Annual Reports/Lists, 1973-1975 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - University Governance, New York University Misc, Oct 1971-May 1976 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - University Governance, Newsletters, Press Coverage, Other Printed Materials, Jun 1967-Dec 1974 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - University Senate, Jan 1976-Mar 1976 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - University Senate, Feb 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - University Senate, Oct 1974-Dec 1974 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - University Senate, Jan 1974-Jul 1974 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224975 8
  - University Senate, Jun 1973-Dec 1973 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - University Senate, Jan 1973-May 1973 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - University Senate, Sep 1972-Dec 1972 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - University Senate, Sep 1971-Jul 1972 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - University Senate, Dec 1969-Mar 1971 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - University Senate Committees, Academic Affairs Committee, Nov 1976-Apr 1977 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - University Senate Committees, Academic Affairs Committee: Time Modules, Dec 1973, Oct 1976-Dec 1976 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - University Senate Committees, All-University Disciplinary Panel, Jun 1974-Dec 1974 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - University Senate Committees, All-University Disciplinary Panel, Jun 1973-May 1974 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - University Senate Committees, Budget Policies Committee, Sep 1976-Apr 1977 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - University Senate Committees, Budget Policies Committee, Apr 1976-Jun 1976 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - University Senate Committees, Budget Policies Committee, Mar 1976 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224976 6
  - University Senate Committees, Budget Policies Committee, Nov 1975-Feb 1976 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - University Senate Committees, Budget Policies Committee, Oct 1974-Jun 1975 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - University Senate Committees, Budget Policies Committee, Sep 1973-May 1974 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - University Senate Committees, Budget Policies Committee, Feb 1972-May 1973 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - University Senate Committees, Educational Policies Committee, Sep 1974-May 1976 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - University Senate Committees, Educational Policies Committee, Mar 1974-Apr 1974 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - University Senate Committees, Educational Policies Committee, Sep 1973-Feb 1974 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - University Senate Committees, Educational Policies Committee, Feb 1971-May 1973 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - University Senate Committees, Educational Policies Committee: Letters on Calendaring, Jan 1973-Mar 1973 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - University Senate Committees, Educational Policies Committee: Reports on Calendaring Issues Elsewhere, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - University Senate Committees, Graduate and Professional Education Committee, Feb 1972-Jan 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224977 4
  - University Senate Committees, Grievance Committee, Nov 1970-May 1973 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - University Senate Committees, Library Advisory Committee, Nov 1975-Mar 1977 (Box 40, Folder 3)